http://www.molsoft.com/terms-of-use.html

Technology Summary
ICM-Modeling (PDF)
Terms of Use
All content on the Molsoft LLC web site located at www.molsoft.com is the exclusive property of Molsoft LLC and is protected by U.S. and international copyright, trademark, trade dress, and other laws. Permission to use the content posted on the Molsoft LLC web site including any and all information, software, descriptive materials, graphics, press releases, video, images, documents, and other materials and services (the "Content"), is granted by Molsoft LLC ("Molsoft") for the use of its customers, employees, and members of the public but only for the lawful purposes described herein and provided that (1) the copyright notice appears in all copies and both the copyright notice and this permission notice appear, (2) use of the Content is for informational and non-commercial or personal use only and will not be copied or posted on any network computer or broadcast in any media, (3) no modifications of any Content is made, and (4) no graphics available from this web site is used separate from the accompanying text. Use for any unauthorized purpose is expressly prohibited by law and may result in prosecution and penalties.
No logo, graphic, or image may be copied or retransmitted unless express permission from Molsoft is first obtained.
In exchange for accessing, browsing and/or using the web site, you agree to be bound by these terms and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations, including without limitation U.S. export and re-export control laws and regulations. You represent that you have the legal authority to accept the terms of use on behalf of yourself or any party you represent.
Your use of the Site constitutes your agreement to all the terms, conditions and notices contained herein.
The web site is controlled and operated by Molsoft from its offices within the United States. BY ACCESSING THE SITE YOU AGREE THAT THE STATUTES AND LAWS OF THE UNITED STATES AND THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA, WITHOUT REGARD TO CONFLICTS OF LAWS PRINCIPLES, WILL APPLY TO ALL MATTERS RELATING TO USE OF THE SITE, AND YOU AGREE THAT ANY LITIGATION SHALL BE SUBJECT TO THE EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION OF THE STATE OR FEDERAL COURTS IN CALIFORNIA. Those who access the Site from other locations do so at their own risk and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. Molsoft makes no representation that the Content in the web site is appropriate or available for use in other locations, and access to it from territories where the Content is illegal is prohibited. You acknowledge that Molsoft reserves the right in its sole discretion to refuse or terminate access to the web site by you at any time.
Disclaimer
While Molsoft makes reasonable efforts to include accurate and up-to-date information on its Server, it makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy. Information of this web site may contain technical inaccuracies or typographical errors and may be changed or updated without notice. Molsoft may also make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or the programs described at any time without notice. Molsoft assumes no liability or responsibility for any typographical or other errors or omissions in the content on this site.
Limitation of Liability
MOLSOFT MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THE CONTENT, THE DOCUMENTS AND RELATED GRAPHICS AND/OR SOFTWARE PUBLISHED ON THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL SUCH CONTENT, DOCUMENTS AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND AND ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE. THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF THEIR USE, THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE, OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE REMAINS WITH THE RECIPIENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL MOLSOFT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION), EVEN IF MOLSOFT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Software
Any and all software ("Software") that is made available to view or download from this web site is owned by and is the copyrighted work of Molsoft and is protected by U.S. and international laws. Use of the Software is governed by the terms of the end user license agreement, if any, which accompanies or is included with the Software ("License Agreement"). You may not install or use any Software that is accompanied by or includes a License Agreement unless you first agree to the License Agreement terms.
The Software is made available for downloading solely for use by end users according to the terms of the applicable License Agreement. Any reproduction or redistribution of the Software not in accordance with the License Agreement is expressly prohibited by law and may result in prosecution and penalties.
WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, COPYING OR REPRODUCTION OF THE SOFTWARE TO ANY OTHER SERVER OR LOCATION FOR FURTHER REPRODUCTION OR REDISTRIBUTION IS EXPRESSLY PROHIBITED.
THE SOFTWARE IS WARRANTED, IF AT ALL, ONLY ACCORDING TO THE TERMS OF THE LICENSE AGREEMENT. EXCEPT AS WARRANTED IN THE LICENSE AGREEMENT, MOLSOFT LLC HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THE SOFTWARE, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL MOLSOFT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION), EVEN IF MOLSOFT HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
RESTRICTED RIGHTS LEGEND. Any Software which is downloaded from this Server for or on behalf of the United States of America, its agencies and/or instrumentalities ("U.S. Government"), is provided with Restricted Rights. Use, duplication, or disclosure by the U.S. Government is subject to restrictions as set forth in subparagraph (c)(1)(ii) of the Rights in Technical Data and Computer Software clause at DFARS 252.227-7013 or subparagraphs (c)(1) and (2) of the Commercial Computer Software -- Restricted Rights at 48 CFR 52.227-19, as applicable. Manufacturer is Molsoft LLC, 11199 Sorrento Valley Road, Ste. 209, San Diego, CA 92121 USA.
Trademarks and Service Marks
Molsoft LLC and the names of Molsoft products referenced on the web site are trademarks and/or service marks or registered trademarks and/or service marks owned by Molsoft.
Molsoft's trademarks and service marks may not be used as a hyperlink without first obtaining Molsoft's written permission.
Your use of Molsoft's trademarks in advertising or promoting Molsoft's projects and services requires an accompanying statement that the trademarks below to Molsoft.
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Other product and company names mentioned herein may be trademarks and/or service marks of their respective owners.
Links to Other Web Sites
LINKED SITES ARE NOT UNDER THE CONTROL OF MOLSOFT, AND MOLSOFT IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT OF ANY LINKED SITE OR ANY LINK CONTAINED IN A LINKED SITE. MOLSOFT PROVIDES LINKS ONLY AS A CONVENIENCE, AND THE INCLUSION OF ANY LINK DOES NOT IMPLY ENDORSEMENT BY MOLSOFT OF THE SITE.
IN NO EVENT WILL MOLSOFT BE LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES FOR ANY USE OF THIS WEBSITE, OR ON ANY OTHER HYPERLINKED WEBSITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY LOST PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF PROGRAMS OR OTHER DATA ON THE USER'S INFORMATION HANDLING SYSTEM OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF MOLSOFT IS EXPRESSLY ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
When you access a linked web site from the Molsoft web site, you acknowledge that Molsoft has no control over the content on that web site. You are responsible for viewing and abiding by the terms of use on any linked sites. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use is free of such items as viruses, worms, Trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature.
Molsoft makes no representation or warranty as to any content or products available from any linked site.
Submission of Information
Molsoft provides certain encryption in an effort to protect the electronic transmission of credit card numbers ("financial information") and other information that you submit through the web site.
Molsoft does not, however, guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the web site. You agree to assume the security risk for any information you provide using the web site.
Your personally identifiable information you submit to us shall be treated in accordance with Molsoft's Privacy Policy.
You are prohibited from posting or transmitting to or from the Site any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, or profane material, or any other material that could give rise to any civil or criminal liability under the law.
Privacy Policy
By agreeing to these Terms and Conditions of Use you also agree you have read and accept Molsoft's privacy policy.
[Updated March 24, 2011]
Copyright © 2020 Molsoft LLC.All rights reserved.Terms of UsePrivacy Policy
